

CONTACTS

- kozarezov.dd@gmail.com
- nttps://github.com/kozarezov

Driver license: B, have a car

Family status: Married, have children

LANGUAGES

English

B2 - Upper Intermediate

SKILLS

• Python

Professional

Django

Experienced

Git

Experienced

Excel

Experienced

C/C++

Basic

PERSONAL QUALITIES

- Fast learning ability
- Communication skills
- Creativity

ХОББИ

- Handwork
- Investing
- Reading literature
- Startups
- Journeys

KOZAREZOV DENIS

PYTHON BACKEND DEVELOPER

Y Krasnodar

Age: 30 years old

ABOUT ME



I have been working in the logistics sector for 10 years.

- In 2020, I was selected for School21 (like a 42 School in France https://42.fr/), at the moment I am studying
- In 2022, I am studying at Yandex Practicum

My projects can be found on GitHub (https://github.com/kozarezov)

I have been working in logistics for 10 years. For the last 2 years, I have been immersed in IT.

My dream is to combine logistics and development

WORK EXPERIENCE -



09.2020 -Present.

SberLogistica

head manager

Optimization of the work of the department.

10.2018 - Present

BG

Director of Logistics

• Own business

Lorus SCM

- Clients: Magnit, X5, Danone, XPO, Constell-Group
- Staff 12 people

02.2018 -

10.2019

Leading Customer Service Manager

- Development and work with clients
- Managing the Logistics and Customer Service managers department

2010

12.2010 - 02.2018

Magnit

Head of the Transport Department

Organization of the work of the logistics and cargo transportation department

EDUCATION



2015

KubSU: Master's degree *Economics, Logistics*

2013

KubSU: Bachelor's degree *Economics, Innovation*

COURSES



2021

School 21Basic training

2022

Yandex Practicum Python Backend